Guide to the Livingston Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- OVERSIZE AND SPECIAL FORMATS, 8; (39 boxes)
  - From Series XI. Curran and Mulford Family Papers
    - Curran, Henry H.
      - Immigration history clippings, 1862-1881 (Box 156, Folder 1247)
      - John Elliott Curran: Vernet print, undated (Box 156, Folder 1248)
  - From Series VIII, Henry H. Livingston: Hudson Valley miscellaneous: USGS maps of Oak Hill area, 1933-1943 (Box 157, Folder 1249)
  - From Series VIII, Henry H. Livingston: Livingston hatchment (photograph), undated (Box 157, Folder 1250)
  - From Series XI: John Elliott Curran: obituaries, 1890 (Box 157, Folder 1251)
  - From Series XI: John Elliott Curran: personal papers, 1866, 1870 (Box 157, Folder 1252)
  - From Series XI: Eliza Mulford Curran: map of Paris, 1905 (Box 157, Folder 1253)
  - From Series XI: Henry H. Curran: military service papers: World War I, 1918, undated (Box 157, Folder 1254)
  - From Series XI, Henry H. Curran: immigration history clippings, 1862-1881 (Box 157, Folder 1255)
  - From Series XII. Other Papers
    - Livingston family portraits, undated (Box 158, Folder 1256-1257)
    - McVitty, Honoria Livingston (1909-2000): wedding portrait and newspaper clipping, 1931 (Box 158, Folder 1258)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Box 158, Folder 1259)
    - Unidentified people, undated (Box 158, Folder 1260-1264)
      Includes Yale and other crew team photographs
    - Unidentified places, undated (Box 158, Folder 1265)
- Special format photographs
  - From Series II. Herman T. and Susan Livingston Papers: Frederic Edwin Church, quarter-plate daguerreotype by Jeremiah Gurney of portrait drawing of Church by Samuel Worcester Rowse (1822-1901), circa 1856 (Box 159, Folder 1266)
  - From Series III. Herman and Emeline H. Livingston Papers: Samuel Mott Cornell (1806-1883), quarter-plate ambrotype in double-sided viewing case, circa 1858 (Box 159, Folder 1267)
  - From Series III. Herman and Emeline H. Livingston Papers: Samuel Mott Cornell (1806-1883), sixth-plate ambrotype in double-sided viewing case, circa 1858 (Box 159, Folder 1268)
  - From Series III. Herman and Emeline H. Livingston Papers: Emeline Howland Cornell (1816-1854), sixth-plate daguerreotype, circa 1854 (Box 159, Folder 1269)
  - From Series III. Herman and Emeline H. Livingston Papers: Unidentified baby [Emeline Hopkins?], quarter-plate ambrotype by Mathew B. Brady in double-sided viewing case, circa 1859 (Box 160, Folder 1270)
  - From Series XI. Curran and Mulford Family Papers: John E. Curran, ninth-plate ambrotype portrait in frame, circa 1858 (Box 160, Folder 1271)
  - From Series XII. Other Papers: Unidentified man, quarter-plate daguerreotype, circa 1855 (Box 160, Folder 1272)
  - From Series XII. Other Papers: Unidentified man, sixth-plate ambrotype in Littlefield, Parsons & Co. union case, circa 1855 (Box 160, Folder 1273)
  - From Series XII. Other Papers: Unidentified woman, sixth-plate opalotype [poor condition], undated (Box 160, Folder 1274)
- Broadside Folders
  - From Series IV: Anna P. Livingston: World War I posters (9), 1918, undated (Box BSD, folder 1275)
  - From Series V: Archibald R. Livingston: Ship plans (4); Big Bend district, Texas (1915); World War I maps (10), circa 1915- 1936 (Box BSD, folder 1276)
  - From Series VIII: Henry and Maria Livingston: genealogical table from The Livingstons of Livingston Manor, 1910 (Box BSD, folder 1277)
  - From Series XI: Henry H. Curran: Military service papers: World War I: maps, 1918, undated (Box BSD, folder 1278)
  - From Series XI: Henry H. Curran: Mayoral campaign poster, 1921 (Box BSD, folder 1279)
- Restricted Fragile Material
  Restricted Fragile Material contains nitrate negatives removed from various series in the Livingston Family Papers. They include negatives made by Anna Livingston (Series IV) and Archibald Livingston (Series V), of photographs in the scrapbook of Henry H. Livingston (Series VII), and loose images seen in Eliza Mulford Curran's papers (Series XI). There are also miscellaneous negatives which were not matched up to any specific family member.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - From Box 114, folder 1012 (Box 161, Folder 1281)
  - Recording of Hon. Henry Curran made by WNYC, Canada Day at New York World's Fair, 1939 July 1; 1; 00:08:29; A test tone briefly overlaps with the main content around 04:47. Surface distortion and noise. Audio pops and clicks. Audio hiss and distortion. The beginning and end of the program are cut off. (Box 161a, Item barcode 39002104615811)
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Nitrate negatives from several series, circa 1908-1922 (Box 162 CS)